# **Ankit Paunikar**

Software Engineer



+91 7715824563



ankitkpaunikar@gmail.com

## **PROJECTS**

**Portfolio Analysis Application** 

Client: IQUW

Oct 2023 to Present

Comprehended Figma to design and develop reuseable UI components,The technology stack

deployed in this project includes React.js, Next.js, TypeScript,

JavaScript, and Node.js, used Azure DevOps to maintain code bases for FE, BE.

**Wealth Management Application** 

Client: UBS

Dec 2022 to Aug 2023

Designed and implemented the UI using Angular, CSS, and Unqork,

Resolved bugs and maintained documents using Jira and Confluence

#### **GIP**

Client: Global Infrastructure

**Partners** 

Jan 2022 to Oct 2022

Ensured the proper flow of communication with the client by making the business workflow diagrams using **lucidchart**, Designed using Figma and developed the UI using HTML, CSS, and Unqork

Prepared and explained application demos to the client. Maintained development timelines using Jira

As a software developer with more than two years of experience, my work involves obtaining and creating application requirements from clients. Proficient in using JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Next.js, Node.js, and Unqork to develop applications. Additionally, I have experience using Jira and **Confluence** for requirement maintenance.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Software Engineer | Oct 2022 to Present Mumbai, India

- Analyzed client requirements and pro-actively coordinated with the team to schedule testing and set development timeframes
- Generated solutions and enhanced code quality using React.js, TypeScript, Next.js, JavaScript, and Node.js for numerous projects
- Delivered client requirements within strict timelines by working on Jira, Confluence, and Azure DevOps

Associate Software Engineer | Oct 2021 to Oct 2022 Mumbai, India

- Assisted the customer with the business workflow and kept up with the application documentation and artifacts
- Efficiently managed time by developing solutions for requirements using HTML, CSS, and Unqork
- Maintained Jira for the timeline of development and plan testing
- Prepared and successfully pitched application demos to the client

### **SKILLS**

- React.js
- Next.js
- Typescript
- Node.js
- Microsoft SQL Server
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Figma
- Tableau
- Unqork

#### **EDUCATION**

Electronics and telecommunication (BE) Ramrao Adik Institution of Technology

Passing year: 2021

Final pointer: 7.01 / 10.00 CGPA